[music]
>> Welcome. My name is Wojciech Kotelko and
today we will be talking about Copilot,
the one and only Copilot. We are
introducing it in Business Central. This
is not the one, this is the old UI.
Uh what you will be seeing
is uh a new Copilot experience in
Business Central. It's a unified
Microsoft Copilot uh experience across
all Microsoft uh products. It has access
to your data from Business Central. It
respects your permissions. It respects
your context
uh and everything that um Microsoft and
Business Central knows about your
activities.
If you have the additional Microsoft
Copilot license,
uh your uh data is also coming from uh
Work IQ. That is your uh calendar, your
emails, your Teams conversations, files
stored on OneDrive or SharePoint and and
more.
This is also very similar to all the
other experiences uh you might have seen
with Microsoft Copilot across other
Microsoft products like uh Word, Excel,
or PowerPoint.
So the best uh way to see it in action
is to show you a little bit of a demo.
All right, so this is uh Business
Central. Of course, this is the latest
release. And as you can see, I have a
Copilot button here.
This button now opens a new experience,
an updated version of um Copilot. This
is powered by Microsoft Copilot uh and
can answer questions about Business
Central
uh data, but also questions that are not
fully related to Business Central.
So let's uh try a very simple example. I
can ask a question about Copilot
features in Business Central.
And of course, Copilot provides me all
the details about various features
in Business Central and data coming from
documentation, from internet and also
with the context of Business Central.
Let's try it a different example. I can
ask for most urgent sales orders.
And I'm asking for
this analysis.
So, in this case, the Copilot search for
data in Business Central. It has access
to my context, my permissions and my
company. And of course, I can open that
data side by side. I can read the
responses from Copilot, but I can also
continue conversations with Copilot. For
instance, I can ask for the fulfillment
backlog for Adatum Corporation because
this sales order specifically is coming
from Adatum.
And
I can go on and on and ask Copilot
various questions about my data.
This in a nutshell is how this new
feature looks like.
Perfect. This was just the first and
simple example.
But you have access to this feature in
your newest Business Central. Just give
it a try. Also, have a look at the next
video in this series where we are
showing more and more detailed examples.
Stay with us.